Iris Kotsinas

ENGINEERING STUDENT



PERSONAL

Iris Kotsinas Name

Birthday November 21, 1997

Nationality Swedish

Language Swedish, English,

(Spanish, Chinese)

ABOUT ME

I am an active and ambitious. 23-year old, Master of Science student with a great interest for game and software development. I strive to apply and develop my programming skills, and I am always open for the opportunity to learn something new.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

C++, C#, TYPESCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT, JAVA, CSS/HTML, PHP, PYTHON, MYSQL, MONGODB, MATLAB, JEST, DOCKER, NEXT.JS, REACT, REACT NATIVE, GRAPHQL, UNITY

LINKS

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/iriskotsinas/ Portfolio: iriskotsinas.github.io/portfolio GitHub: github.com/iriskotsinas

CONTACT

Mobile +46 735 108 508 Email iris.kotsinas@gmail.com

Address Nygatan 61

602 34 Norrköping

EDUCATION

Linköping University Norrköping, SE - M.Sc. in Media Technology and Engineering 2017 - present

Programming, computer graphics, visualization and design.

Relevant selected courses

Object-oriented programming TND002 3D-Computer Graphics **TNM061** Communication and user interfaces TNM040 Modelling and simulation **TNG022** Practical Data Visualization and Virtual Reality TNM094 Machine Learning for Social Media **TNM108** Global Illumination and Rendering TNGC15 TNM079 Modelling and Animation Artificial Intelligence Principles and Techniques **TNM096**

Eastern High School Louisville, KY, USA

- High School Exchange Year - STS 2014-2015

Danderyds Gymnasium (High School) Stockholm, SE 2013-2017 - Science program, international focus

EXPERIENCE

We Know IT Sweden AB Linköping, SE - Software Developer 2021/01 - present

Part-time consultant at We Know IT, a student-run

IT-consultancy firm.

Upsales Nordic AB Linköping, SE

- System Developer 2021/06 - 2021/08

Extended Upsales' booking system, Easy Booking. (TypeScript, React, Node.js, MySQL)

Netlight Consulting AB

Stockholm, SE - Student Brand Manager 2020/09 - 2021/06

Promoted and created Netlight events for students at Linköping University

Linköping University Norrköping, SE

- Teaching Assistant, Applied Transform Theory 2021/01 - 2021-03 Assist students in the course TNG032 Applied 2020/01 - 2020/03 Transform Theory (MATLAB)

- Teaching Assistant, Electronic Publishing 2020/11 - 2021/01 Assisted students in the course TNMK30 Electronic 2019/11 - 2020/01 Publishing (HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS and MySQL)

Axis Communications AB

Linköping, SE Software Developer Intern 2020/06 - 2020/08

Developed a software for Axis surveillance cameras (TypeScript, Next.js, mongoose, Express, Docker and more)

EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

Media Technology Days 2020 2019-2020

- Economy manager

Norrköpings Akademiska Förening för Idrott 2019-2020

Sponsorship manager

2018-2019 Women's association Mette

- Economy manager

2019 Swedish women's national lacrosse team

- Player

REFERENCES

Available on request.